Guide to the Wallace Notestein Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Wallace Notestein papers
1899-1969
MS 544
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.25
The papers consist of correspondence, writings, printed material, notes, speeches, and other papers of Wallace Notestein, historian, teacher, author, and Sterling Professor of English History at Yale from 1928-1947. The bulk of the papers consist of letters received by Notestein from other historians, scholars, writers, students, and publishers and relate largely to academic and professional matters, to politics, and to his personal life.
Notestein, Wallace, 1878-1969
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ada Louise Comstock Notestein, 1970.
Arrangement
Arranged in six series: I. Correspondence. II. Manuscripts. III. Printed Material. IV. Subject File. V. Letters of Sympathy. VI. Ada Comstock Notestein.
Scope and Contents
The Notestein Papers consist primarily of personal correspondence, a diary, notes, speeches, and writings, 1906-1958, printed matter (primarily newspaper clippings), and a subject file pertaining to the History Department, various awards, the Parliamentary Diaries Project, Yale University Press, and a class reunion for the College of Wooster, 1902-1910. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of the writer of the letter, and covers the years 1899 to 1969. Included are personal and general correspondence relating to historical writings and academic careers, including letters to Notestein from such distinguished scholars as Hugh Trevor-Roper, Perry Miller, Hartly Simpson, John E. Neale, Ulrich B. Phillips, Alan Nevins, Lewis P. Curtis, Carl Becker, Charles Beard, Samuel Flagg Bemis, Leonard Labaree, Samuel E. Morison, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Sr., E. L. Woodward, and others.
Wallace Notestein (December 16, 1578-1969) was born in Wooster, Ohio; son of Jonas O, and Margaret (Wallace) Notestein. He married Ada Louise Comstock, June 14, 1943. He received his B. A. from Wooster in 1900 and his Ph. D. from Yale in 1908. In addition, he received honorary degrees from Wooster, Litt. D., 1923, Harvard 1939, Birmingham 1950, Yale 1951, Oxford 1958, and Glasgow, LL., D., 1950. Notestein was assistant professor of history, University of Kansas, 1905-1907; instructor of history, University of Minnesota, 1908; assistant professor, 1910, associate professor, 1914, professor, 1917-1920; professor of English History, Cornell, 1920-1928; Sterling Professor English History, Yale, 1928-1947, emeritus, 1947-; Eastman Professor Oxford University, 1949-1950; fellow Balliol College, 1949-1950; Research Assistant, Committee on Public Information, 1917; attached to State Department, 1918, American Commission to Negotiate Peace, Paris, 1919; member of British Commission appointed by Prime Minister, House of Commons Records, 1929-1932; member of Advisory Council, Guggenheim Foundation, 1939-1948; Corresponding Fellow, British Academy; member of the American Philosophical Society, Massachusetts Historical Society, Phi Gamma Delta. Notestein was a member of the Century Club (NYC) and the Athenaeum (London). Known as a gifted writer and an authority on English life and government of the 17th century, Notestein produced the following books:
› History of English Witchcraft, 1913
› Source Problems in English History, 1915 (with A. B. White)
› Commons Debates, 1629-1921 (with Frances H. Relf)
› D'Ewes Journal of the Long Parliament, 1923
› Winning of the Initiative by the House of Commons (Raleigh lecture, British Academy), 1924
› Commons Debates 1621, 7 vols., 1935 (with F. H. Relf, H. Simpson)
› English Folk, 1938
› The Scot in History, 1946
› The English People on the Eve of Colonization, 1954
› Four Worthies, 1956
The Notestein Papers consist primarily of personal correspondence, a diary, notes, speeches, and writings, 1906-1958, printed matter (primarily newspaper clippings), and a subject file pertaining to the History Department, various awards, the Parliamentary Diaries Project, Yale University Press, and a class reunion for the College of Wooster, 1902-1910. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of the writer of the letter, and covers the years 1899 to 1969. Included are personal and general correspondence relating to historical writings and academic careers, including letters to Notestein from such distinguished scholars as Hugh Trevor-Roper, Perry Miller, Hartly Simpson, John E. Neale, Ulrich B. Phillips, Alan Nevins, Lewis P. Curtis, Carl Becker, Charles Beard, Samuel Flagg Bemis, Leonard Labaree, Samuel E. Morison, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Sr., E. L. Woodward, and others.
Wallace Notestein (December 16, 1578-1969) was born in Wooster, Ohio; son of Jonas O, and Margaret (Wallace) Notestein. He married Ada Louise Comstock, June 14, 1943. He received his B. A. from Wooster in 1900 and his Ph. D. from Yale in 1908. In addition, he received honorary degrees from Wooster, Litt. D., 1923, Harvard 1939, Birmingham 1950, Yale 1951, Oxford 1958, and Glasgow, LL., D., 1950. Notestein was assistant professor of history, University of Kansas, 1905-1907; instructor of history, University of Minnesota, 1908; assistant professor, 1910, associate professor, 1914, professor, 1917-1920; professor of English History, Cornell, 1920-1928; Sterling Professor English History, Yale, 1928-1947, emeritus, 1947-; Eastman Professor Oxford University, 1949-1950; fellow Balliol College, 1949-1950; Research Assistant, Committee on Public Information, 1917; attached to State Department, 1918, American Commission to Negotiate Peace, Paris, 1919; member of British Commission appointed by Prime Minister, House of Commons Records, 1929-1932; member of Advisory Council, Guggenheim Foundation, 1939-1948; Corresponding Fellow, British Academy; member of the American Philosophical Society, Massachusetts Historical Society, Phi Gamma Delta. Notestein was a member of the Century Club (NYC) and the Athenaeum (London). Known as a gifted writer and an authority on English life and government of the 17th century, Notestein produced the following books:
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Great Britain -- History; Historians; Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971; Aiken, William Appleton, 1907-1957; Andrews, Charles McLean, 1863-1943; Andrews, Evangeline Walker; Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949; Austen, Willard; Aydelotte, Frank, 1880-1956; Aydelotte, William Osgood, 1910-1996; Babb, James T. (James Tinkham), 1899-1968; Bacon, Leonard, 1887-1954; Bahlman, Dudley W. R.; Bainton, Roland H. (Roland Herbert), 1894-1984; Barbour, Violet, 1884-1968; Baxter, James Phinney, 1831-1921; Beard, Charles A. (Charles Austin), 1874-1948; Becker, Carl L. (Carl Lotus), 1873-1945; Bemis, Samuel Flagg, 1891-1973; Benét, William Rose, 1886-1950; Bingham, Alfred M. (Alfred Mitchell), 1905-1998; Blackburn, Katharine C.; Blum, John Morton, 1921-2011; Bourne, Edward Gaylord, 1860-1908; Bourne, Henry Eldridge, 1862-1946; Bowman, Isaiah, 1878-1950; Brooks, Van Wyck, 1886-1963; Buchan, John, 1875-1940; Buchanan, Harvey; Buck, Solon J. (Solon Justus), 1884-1962; Buckler, W. H. (William Hepburn), 1867-1952; Bullard, F. Lauriston (Frederic Lauriston), 1866-1952; Bush, Vannevar, 1890-1974; Butterfield, Herbert, 1900-1979; Canby, Henry Seidel, 1878-1961; Canfield, Cass, 1897-1986; Cape, Jonathan, 1879-1960; Chafee, Zechariah, Jr., 1885-1957; Chase, Mary Ellen, 1887-1973; Clapp, Moses E. (Moses Edwin), 1851-1929; Commager, Henry Steele, 1902-1998; Compton, K. T. (Karl Taylor), 1887-1954; Comstock, Ada Louise; Conant, James Bryant, 1893-1978; Converse, Allen Dean, 1911-; Corwin, Robert Nelson, 1864-1944; Coulton, G. G. (George Gordon), 1858-1947; Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948; Cruikshank, R. J. (Robert James), 1898-1956; Curtis, Lewis Perry, 1900-1976; Daiches, David, 1912-2005; Davis, Malcolm W. (Malcolm Waters), 1889-1970; DeVane, William C. (William Clyde), 1898-1965; Dodd, William E. (William Edward), 1869-1940; Donovan, William J., 1905-; Dow, Sterling, 1903-1995; Dumond, Dwight Lowell, 1895-1976; Durand, Albert C.; Evans, Paul Demund; Farnam, Thomas Wells, 1877-1943; Farrand, Livingston, 1867-1939; Farrand, Max, 1869-1945; Ford, Guy Stanton, 1873-1962; Ford, Worthington Chauncey, 1858-1941; Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1887-1945; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965; Furniss, Edgar S. (Edgar Stevenson), 1890-1972; Gage, Harry M.; Geyl, Pieter, 1887-1966; Gooch, G. P. (George Peabody), 1873-1968; Gottschalk, Louis Reichenthal, 1899-1975; Gras, Norman Scott Brien, 1884-1956; Graves, Henry Solon, 1871-1951; Hackett, Francis, 1883-1962; Hadley, Helen Harrison Morris, 1864-1939; Haight, Gordon Sherman; Haring, C. H. (Clarence Henry), 1885-1960; Harsch, Joseph C. (Joseph Close), 1905-; Haskins, Charles Homer, 1870-1937; Hayes, Carlton J. H. (Carlton Joseph Huntley), 1882-1964; Henning, Basil Duke; Hersey, John, 1914-1993; Hexter, J. H. (Jack H.), 1910-1996; Hicks, John D., 1890-1972; Hilles, Frederick W. (Frederick Whiley), 1900-1975; Holden, Reuben A. (Reuben Andrus), 1918-; Howe, Quincy, 1900-1977; Jameson, J. Franklin (John Franklin), 1859-1937; Jordan, W. K. (Wilbur Kitchener), 1902-1980; Kirchwey, George W. (George Washington), 1855-1942; Krock, Arthur, 1886-1974; Labaree, Leonard Woods, 1897-1980; Lamar, Howard Roberts, 1923-; Lamb, W. Kaye (William Kaye), 1904-; Leland, Waldo Gifford, 1879-1966; Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert), 1887-; Lonergan, Augustine, 1874-1947; Loveman, Amy; Lovett, Sidney, 1890-1979; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982; Macmillan, Harold, 1894-1986; Maitland, E. M. (Edward Maitland), 1880-1921; Malone, Dumas, 1892-1986; Manning, Helen Taft, 1891-1987; Mendenhall, Thomas C. (Thomas Corwin), 1841-1924; Merriman, Roger Bigelow, 1876-1945; Merz, Charles, 1893-; Miller, Perry, 1905-1963; Moe, Henry Allen, 1894-1975; Morgan, Edmund S. (Edmund Sears), 1916-2013; Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1887-1976; Mowat, R. B. (Robert Balmain), 1883-1941; Munro, Dana Carleton, 1866-1933; Namier, L. B. (Lewis Bernstein), 1888-1960; Neale, J. E. (John Ernest), 1890-1975; Nettleton, George Henry, 1874-1959; Nevins, Allan, 1890-1971; Nicoll, Allardyce, 1894-1976; Northrop, Cyrus, 1834-1922; Notestein, Wallace, 1878-1969; Osgood, Herbert L. (Herbert Levi), 1855-1918; Packard, Laurence Bradford, 1887-1955; Pares, Richard, 1902-1958; Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1909-1975; Perkins, Dexter, 1889-1984; Phillips, Ulrich Bonnell, 1877-1934; Pierson, George Wilson, 1904-1993; Plumb, J. H. (John Harold), 1911-2001; Polk, Frank L. (Frank Lyon), 1871-1943; Pollard, A. F. (Albert Frederick), 1869-1948; Prescott, Orville, 1906-; Read, Conyers, 1881-1959; Rostovtzeff, Michael Ivanovitch, 1870-1952; Rostow, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1913-2002; Rowse, A. L. (Alfred Leslie), 1903-1997; Rudin, Harry R. (Harry Rudolph), 1898-; Scammon, Richard E., 1883-1952; Schlesinger, Arthur M. (Arthur Meier), 1888-1965; Schmitt, Bernadotte Everly, 1886-1969; Seymour, Charles, 1885-1963; Seymour, George Dudley, 1859-1945; Simpson, Hartley; Sitwell, George Reresby, Sir, 1860-1943; Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1874-1958; Sweet, Henry Gordon, 1904-1975; Tawney, R. H. (Richard Henry), 1880-1962; Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1876-1963; Toynbee, Arnold, 1889-1975; Trevor-Roper, H. R. (Hugh Redwald), 1914-2003; Van Doren, Irita Taylor, 1891-1966; Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930; Wallace, DeWitt, 1889-1981; Wedgwood, C. V. (Cicely Veronica), 1910-1997; Wedgwood, Josiah C. (Josiah Clement), 1872-1943; Welles, C. Bradford (Charles Bradford), 1901-1969; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944; Woodward, E. L. (Ernest Llewellyn), 1890-1971; Worcester, Dean Kirkham, 1922-; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. Department of History
- Correspondence, 1899-1969; Series I; (11 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I contains correspondence of Wallace Notestein from 1899 to 1969. The letters are arranged alphabetically by correspondent, with unidentifiable and undated material at the end.
  - Abbott, Wilbur C., 1905-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abraham, Louis A., 1929-1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acheson, Dean, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, E. D., 1916 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adams, George B., 1906-1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adams, John H., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Kerney M., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Randolph G., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, W., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Aiken, William A., 1940-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Airey, George F. M., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alexander, Margaret C., 1919 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Martha A., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Clara, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Frank M., 1913-1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Anderson, William, 1912-1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Andrews, Charles and Evangeline, 1910-1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Angell, James R., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Archibald, W., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Armstrong, Aileen M., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ashton, John, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assheton, Ralph, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Atchison, Blanche, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Atkinson, Frank P., 1902 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Atkinson, R. L., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Austen, Willard, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Austin, Roland, 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Axtell, Winifred, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Aydelotte, Frank, 1928-1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aydelotte, William, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Aylmer, G. E., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Babb, James J., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bacon, Leonard, 1939-1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bacon, Paul V., 1912 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bagshawe, F. E. G., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bahlman, Dudley, 1957-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Additional correspondence, 1957-1969 (Box 10A, Folder 843-852)
  - Bailey, Susan, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bainton, Roland, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ball, Katherine, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bandson, Louise K., undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Barber, M. A., 1908-1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Barbour, Violet, 1936-1955 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Barnes, Thomas G., 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Barrell, Joseph, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Barringham, Hugh, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Baumer, Frank, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Baxter, James P., 1937-1948 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Beard, Charles A., 1934, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bechtold, Grace, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Becker, Carl, 1908, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Becket, Jean C., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Beer, Edith C., 1920 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bell, H. C., 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bell, Lila, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bemis, Samuel Flagg, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Benet, Rosemary (Mrs Stephen Vincent), undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Benet, William Rose, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bennett, W. Z., 1902 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Berkeley, Francis L., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Berkeley, Mary, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Berquist, Goodwin F., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bickley, Francis, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Biddle, Margaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bingham, Alfred M., undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Birch, W. deGray, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bishop, W. J., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Black, J. G., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Blackburn, Katherine C., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Blakely, George T., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Blaser, Esther H., 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Blayney, F. S., 1900 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bledisloe, Lord, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Blum, John, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bond, M. F., 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Booher, Mary M., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Booth, Joan, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Bosye, Arthur H., 1907 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bourcier, Elizabeth, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bourne, Edward G. and Anne, 1905-1907 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bourne, Henry E., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Bowden, George K. and John, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Bowman, I., 1911-1919 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Boyle, John W., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Boynton, Arthur J., 1906-1909 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Brace, Donald, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Brentano's, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Brett, George P., 1944, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Bridges, T. E., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Brinson, F. W., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Bronson, Marcia, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Brooke, Tucker, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Brooks, Harold F., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Broome, Dorothy M., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Brown, Edward E., 1907 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Brown, E. G. Grant, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Brown, J. Howard, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Brown, Lester and Margaret, 1905, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Brown, L. Parmly, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Brown, L. R., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Brown, Louise Fargo, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Brown, K. D., 1906 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Bryant, Ann, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Bryant, Arthur, 1930-1954 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Buchan, John, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Buchanan, Harvey, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Buck, Paul H., 1919-1944 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Buck, S. B., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Buck, Solon J., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Buckler, William H., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Bullard, F. Lauriston, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Burbank, Edmund G., undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Burbridge, Charles, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Burch, Aline, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Burr, George L., 1906-1937 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Burton, M. L., 1918 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Busey, Garetta, 1928, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Bush, Vannevar, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Butler, Eleanor B., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Butler, Harold E. and Margaret L., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Butler, J. R. M., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Butler, William G., 1933 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Butman, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Butterfield, H., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Caldwell, Theodore C., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Cam, Helen, 1948-1955 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Campbell, Mildred L., 1944, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Campion, G., 1921-1955 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Canby, Henry S., 1929-1936 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Canfield, Cass, 1947-1962 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Cantrall, C. M., 1901 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Cape, Jonathan, 1935-1958 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Carpenter, Reid, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Carr, Ralph, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Carrington, Charles E., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Carritt, E. F., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Carter, M., undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Cathcart, Elizabeth J., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Caton, L. C., 1932- (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Chaddock, Robert E., 1902 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Chafee, Z. Jr., 1939-1951 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Chalk, John, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Chase, A., undated (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Chase, Mary Ellen, 1936, undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Chase, Russell M., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Christie, Ian R., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Churchill, Sue, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Clapham, J. H., 1938, undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Clapp, Moses E., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Clapp, S. H., 1908-1912 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Clark, Dora Mae, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Clark, G. Kitson, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Clark, G. N., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Clark, Henry C., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Clark, Keith, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Clarke, Mary P., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Clarke, M. V., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Coakley, Thomas, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Coates, Willson H., 1928-1947 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Cobbon, Alfred, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Comber, E. Phillip, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Commager, Henry S., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Compton, Karl T., 1930 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Compton, Oletia, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Conant, James B., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Converse, Allen, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Cook, Albert, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Cooke, Anne, undated (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Cooper, John, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Cooper, Louise Field, undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Cooper, Martha G., 1902 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Copeland, Thomas W., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Corbett, Grace, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Corwin, Robert N. and Margaret B., 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Corwin, Margaret T., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Coulton, G. G., 1938-1941 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Coupland, R., undated (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Covey, Katherine K., 1929, undated (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Cowell, Richard and Lilian, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Cowles, Frank H., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Cox, Stokes, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Craigie, William A., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Craster, H. H. E., 1933 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Cratton, Henry, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Crofts, F. S., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Cromwell, Otilia, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Crosby, Sal and Sumner, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1917-1928 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Cross, wilbur L., 1927-1929 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Cruikshank, R. J., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Crump, C. G., 1927, undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Cumberledge, G. F. J., 1932 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Currier, Helen Hill, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Curtis, Jane E. S., undated (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Curtis, Lewis P., 1932-1958 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Curtis, Perry and Alison, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Curtiss, Joseph T., 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Custer, George A., 1899 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Daiches, David, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Dana, Maria Trumbull, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Daubercies, Audrey, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - David, Charles W., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - David, J. N., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Davidson, Eugene, 1937-1968 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Davies, Godfrey, 1928-1943 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Davis, E. J., 1956 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Davis, Herbert, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Davis, Malcolm W., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Davis, Ralph, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Davis, Wiliam S., 1911-1929 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - de Burgh, Alfred, 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Deckman, Carrie W. (Mrs Edward J.), undated (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - DeVane, William and Mabel, 1934-1950 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Dickerson, F. B., 1905-1906 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Dickey, June C., 1912, undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Dodd, A. H., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Dodd, William E., 1920-1935 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Dodd, William F., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Dodds, George E., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Dodds, H. W., 1935 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Dollard, Charles, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Donaldson, Jessie L., 1912, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Donovan, William J., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Dougall, Richardson, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Dow, Sterling, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Drew, Helen L., 1929 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Driver, C. H., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Duckworth, Gerald, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Dumond, Dwight L., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Dunham, Aileen, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Dunham, William, 1937-1968 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Dunlap, Bertha, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Dunlop, Annie, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Durand, Albert C., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Eastman, Anne L., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Edgar, Marjorie, 1935, undated (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Educational Review, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Ehrin, Lionel, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Ehrman, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Elliott, Richard Michael, undated (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Ellis, Frank, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Ellis, Roger, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Elmhirst, Dorothy and Leonard, 1929-1939, undated (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Elton, Lord, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 246)